leadscon.com 2013-10-05

# LeadsCon » Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information (“Information”) by LeadsConference, a wholly owned subsidiary of Access Intelligence, LLC (together with its affiliated entities, “LeadsCon”) in connection with its operation of the Web site located at www.leadscon.com (the “Site”). LeadsCon takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure users are fully informed about the Information they are providing to it.

### Information Collection

LeadsCon does not require any information in order to interact with the site. We do use web beacons, referred to as cookies, which collect limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a web page. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

### Personally Identifiable Information

Certain information collected falls under personally identifiable information, and it is information that allows you to be identified in particular, such as your name, address or phone number. LeadsCon does require certain types of personal information when you register for an event and can include – your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and credit card information.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

There are some occasions when your information will be shared with third parties and includes your name, email address, and title. Your purchase information will always remain confidential, and unless will not be kept on file by LeadsCon. From time to time we may send registrants and members of our newsletter a sponsored message on behalf of our sponsors and/or advertisers. In addition, we may share aggregate but non-personally identifiable information regarding registrants of the shows.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

LeadsCon does not market to nor seek users under the age of 13. Information discovered to contain personally identifiable information on an individual under the age of thirteen will be immediately purged and never shared with third parties.

### Note to California Users

Individual customers who reside in California and have provided their personal information to us may request information about our disclosures of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at privacy(at)leadscon.com. Within thirty days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change, from time to time, due to changes on our web pages, changes in our business, and technology advances, among other factors. Changes will be updated on this page, with the date of last update located below, or you may email privacy(at)leadscon.com for the latest version. _Last Updated September 19, 2012_
